A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security, 2005-2013
The Library of Virginia
51141
7.35 cu. ft. (21 boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security on 9 January 2014.
Biographical/Historical Information
In 2010 Governor Robert F. McDonnell initiated legislative action which changed and re-organized the former Office of Commonwealth Preparedness (OCP) into the Office of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security (OVAHS). With this legislation the Department of Veterans Services (DVS) was moved from the Office of Public Safety to the Office of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security along with the Virginia War Memorial. In April of 2011 Terrie L. Suit was appointed by Governor McDonnell to the position of Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security after previously serving as Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness. James W. Hopper was appointed Deputy Secretary. She stepped down from the position on September 22nd, 2013 after being selected as the Chief Executive Office of the Virginia Association of REALTORS (VAR). Hopper, a previous staff member of McDonnell's tenure as Attorney General from 2006-2009 took over the Secretary's position until January 2014.
The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness had originated from Governor James Gilmore's Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel created after the September 11th terrorist attacks to better prevent and respond to such attacks in Virginia. Shortly thereafter, Governor-elect Mark R. Warner named John H. Hager to the newly created position of assistant to the governor for commonwealth preparedness, now a cabinet-level position, on 28 December 2001. Hager served as lieutenant governor under Governor James Gilmore and was a member of the Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel. On 31 January 2002, Governor Warner issued Executive Order 7, also known as the Secure Virginia Initiative, which rescinded Gilmore's Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel. Executive Order 7 also created the Secure Virginia Panel to review, evaluate, and make recommendations relating to emergency preparedness for the Commonwealth. The Secure Virginia Panel, which became the Secure Commonwealth Panel under Executive Order 69, was to consist of twenty members, later increased to twenty-eight members, under the Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness as chairman. The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness and the Secure Commonwealth Panel were later codified under 2.2-304 through 2.2-306 of the Code of Virginia.
The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness was created with the purpose of developing a coordinated security and preparedness strategy and implementation plan. The Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness, who is appointed by the governor for a term of four years, is responsible for the general management of the Office. The Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security, was later renamed Secretary of Veterans and Defense Affairs by Governor Terry McAuliffe in 2014, with Homeland Security transferred to the Secretary of Public Safety, (renamed Secretary of Public Safety and Homeland Security).
Scope and Content
The Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security records, 2010-2013, consist of 21 boxes divided into eight series. These records document the work of Secretary Terrie L. Suit and the Office of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security during Governor Robert F. McDonnell's gubernatorial term. Includes correspondence, legislative files, decision briefs, meeting records, as well as project and subject files. The bulk of the records can relate to base closings, campus security, hurricane preparedness, interoperability, the National Capital Region, and various office projects.
Some of the key initiatives, advisory boards, and task forces during Suit's tenure included the standardization of emergency radio communication, critical infrastructure protection, commonwealth interoperability and preparedness against terrorist attacks, and campus preparedness. Included among the various types of records are agendas, correspondence, minutes, newsletters, memoranda, programs, reports, and surveys. Researchers should search across series as some issues, offices, and subjects are cross referenced or exist in various series.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Secretary's correspondence, 2010-2013
Series II: Correspondence with the Dept. of Veterans Affairs, 2010-2013
Series III: Constituent correspondence, 2010-2013
Series IV: Legislative files, 2010-2013
Series V: Decision briefs, 2010-2013
Series VI: Meeting records, 2010-2013
Series VII: Project files, 2010-2013
Series VIII: Subject files, 2010-2013.
Related Material
The Governor Robert F. McDonnell Administration Web Archive Collection, 2010-2014 contains archived versions of websites for the Governor's Office, his initiative sites, and the sites of his cabinet secretaries, including the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security and Secretary of Public Safety.
The Records of the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety Collection includes material from the office during Gov. Robert F. McDonnell's tenure.
The Records of Governor Robert F. McDonnell's Secretary of Transportation Collection
The Records of Governor Robert F. McDonnell's Secretary of Administration Collection
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence - Office of the Secretary, 2010-2013., Extent: 2.1 cu. ft. (6 boxes).
  This series includes both the incoming and outgoing correspondence of the Secretary Suit.
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 May. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 May. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 June. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 June. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 July. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 May. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 May. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 June. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 June. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 July. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 July. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Ougoing, 2011 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Ouxtgoing, 2011 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Ougoing, 2011 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 May. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 May. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 June. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 June. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 July. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 July. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Feb 7. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 May. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 May. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 June. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 June. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Aug. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Aug. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Nov. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Nov. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2013 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2013 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Series II. Correspondence - Dept. of Veterans Services, 2010-2013., Extent: .2 cu. ft. (1 box).
  Correspondence with the Dept. of Veterans Services is arranged chronologically and includes both incoming and outgoing correspondence. Topics include audits, board appointments, budget, resignations, Virginia War Memorial, and the Wounded Warrior Program, among others.
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2010. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2010. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2011. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2011. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 2012. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2012. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Incoming and outgoing, 2013. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Series III. Constituent correspondence regarding military retirements, 2010-2013., Extent: .2 cu. ft. (1 box).
  Constituent correspondence regarding military retirements includes both incoming and outgoing correspondence and is arranged chronologically. This series consists of incoming correspondence from U. S. military branches to the Governor requesting retirement letters for Virginia residents. These letters were forwarded to the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security for response. This series in incomplete and includes correspondence for 2010 Jan-Apr; 2011 Oct-Dec; 2012 Jan-Dec; and 2013 Jan-Feb.
  - Correspondence, 2010 Jan-Feb. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2010 Mar-Apr. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2011 Oct-Dec. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2012 Jan-Apr. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2012 May-Sept. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 2012 Oct-Dec. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 2013 Jan-Feb. (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Series IV. Legislative files, 2010-2013., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  Legislative files document proposed legislation related to veterans affairs and homeland security, as well as the 2012-2014 biennial budget. Proposed legislation files may include correspondence, enrolled bill review, fiscal impact statements, key points, legislative action summaries, memoranda, statements of need, tracking sheets.
  - Biennial budget bill (2012-2014) - Communication for the Governor, 2011 Dec 19. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Biennial budget bill (2012-2014) - HB 29, 2012 Jan 11. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Biennial budget bill (2012-2014) - Executive Amendments, 2012 Dec. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Biennial budget bill (2012-2013), 2013 May 3. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Proposed legislation, 2010. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Proposed legislation, 2011. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Proposed legislation, 2012. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Proposed legislation, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1304 Tax credits for contracting with SWAM vendors, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1306 Commission on Federal Oversight Report, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1409 Partipation in public school interscholastic programs by students of military families, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1523 Sales and use tax exemption for hurricane preparedness equipment, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1906 Dept. of Veterans Services - Programs to reduce unemployment among veterans, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 2027 In-state tuition for active duty family members, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 2038 Fort Monroe Authority - Fees in lieu of property taxes, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 2042 Dept. of Motor Vehicles - Customer service, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 2146 Dept. of Veterans Services - Virginia War Memorial Division, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 2175 Veterans Care Center in Northern Virginia, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 2231 Virginia Military Survivors and Dependents Education Fund, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 2280 Freedom of Information Act - Exempt records for disaster preparedness plans, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 701 State government employment non-discrimination, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 730 Sales and use tax exemption for non-profit entities - Veterans organizations, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 766 Sales and use tax exemption for hurricane preparedness equipment, 2013. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 829 Dept. of Veterans Services - Programs to reduce unemployment among veterans, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 830 Voting by military and overseas citizens - Pilot program, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 831 Tax credits for hiring military veterans, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 857 Higher Education - In-state tuition for certain military dependents, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 874- Absentee voting - Return of military overseas ballots, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 897 Memorialization of fallen soldiers at the Virginia War Memorial, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 991 Dept. of Veterans Services - Veteran identification card and discounts on state operated attractions, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 1064 Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security - Powers and duties, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Proposed legislation: SB 1079 Dept. of Medical Assistance Services - Waivers for dependents of military personnel, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1461 and SB 1242 Eligibility for in-state tuition for military, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1750 and SB 1191 Regulation concerning admission of military dependents to school, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Proposed legislation: HB 1853 and SB 1029 Inclusion of military installations planning, zoning and development, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Proposed legislation: HJR 551 Property tax exemption, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Series V. Decision memoranda, 2010-2013., Extent: 1.4 cu. ft. (4 boxes).
  Decision briefs, 2010-2013, are arranged chronologically and document decision requests sent to the Governor for approval. Briefs include background information, discussion and summary, as well as tracking sheets and include recommendations, comments and signatures. The decision brief file may also include reports and correspondence. Topics may include appointments, commissions, communication, disaster preparedness, emergency operations, Fort Monroe, grants, interoperability, Military Strategic Response Fund, staffing, proclamations, Secure Commonwealth Panel, veterans, Virginia War Memorial, Wall of Honor ceremony, and the Wounded Warrior Program.
  - Decision memoranda, 2010 Feb-Mar. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Decision memoranda, 2010 Apr-May. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Decision memoranda, 2010 June-July. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Decision memoranda, 2010 Aug-Sept. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Decision memoranda, 2010 Oct. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Decision memoranda, 2010 Nov. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Decision memoranda, 2010 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Decision memoranda - Touchstone / SRA contract renewal, 2010. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 Jan. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 Feb-Mar. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 Apr. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 Apr. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 May. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 June-July. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 Aug-Sept. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 Oct-Nov. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Decision memoranda, 2011 Dec. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Decision memoranda - Status updates, 2011. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Decision memoranda - Statewide Communications Strategic Plan, 2011. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Decision memoranda, 2012 Jan. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Decision memoranda, 2012 Feb-Mar. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Decision memoranda, 2012 Apr-July. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Decision memoranda, 2012 Aug-Sept. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Decision memoranda, 2012 Oct-Dec. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Decision memoranda - Status updates, 2012. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 Jan. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 Feb. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 Mar. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 Apr-June. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 May. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 July-Oct. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 Nov. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 Nov. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Decision memoranda, 2013 Dec. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Series VI. Meeting records, 2010-2013., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  Meeting records, 2010-2013, are arranged alphabetically by name of entity. These records document the meetings, activities, discussions, policy decisions, and recommendations are various boards and commissions related to the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security. Files may include agendas, handouts, lists of attendees, maps, meeting notes, minutes, presentations, reports, and other supporting material.
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities - Joint Forces Command Work Group, 2010 Jan 6. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities, 2010 Sept 9. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities, 2010 Sept 9. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities - Joint Forces Command Work Group, 2010 Oct 4. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities - Joint Forces Command Work Group, 2010 Nov 17. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities, 2011 July 20. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities - Dept. of Defense / Military Strategies Work Group, 2012 Mar 22. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities - Joint Forces Command Work Group, 2012 Aug 21. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities, 2012 Sept 18. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Military Installations and Defense Activities, 2013 Apr 29. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Military Installations and Defense Activities, 2013 May 28. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Local Military Advisory Council, 2012 Apr 2. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Local Military Advisory Council, 2012 June 14. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Local Military Advisory Council, 2012 Aug 22. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local Military Advisory Council, 2012 Oct 24. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Local Military Advisory Council, 2013 Mar 1. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Local Military Advisory Council, 2013 May 28. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Local Military Advisory Council, 2013 Aug 28. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - National Emergency Grant Development Team, 2013 Feb 14. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Oceana Fentress Military Advisorty Council, 2011 Mar 4. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Oceana Fentress Military Advisorty Council, 2012 July 11. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2010 Aug 11. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2010 Oct 27. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2011 Apr 27. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2011 Nov 14. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2012 June 12. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2012 Oct 10. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - 9-1-1 Sub-Panel, 2012 Sept 5. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - 9-1-1 Sub-Panel, 2012 Sept 26. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - State to State Comparisons, 2011 Aug. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Commission on Military Bases - Report, 2005. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2010 Apr 20. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2010 July 14. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2010 Sept 29. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2010 Nov 9. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2011 Mar 9. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2011 May 11. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2011 Sept 28. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2012 Apr 24. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2012 Oct 18. (Box 17, Folder 2)